Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) records, 1846-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean’s Files 1916-2008
  - 1946-1947
    - Research Projects (Box 76)
    - Resignations (Box 76)
    - Retirements (Box 76)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Trust (Box 76)
    - Rid-Ros, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 76)
    - Rosen-Rz, 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Russian, Department of (Box 76)
    - Saa-Sph, 11 folders (Box 76)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 76)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 76)
    - Spi-Std (Box 76)
    - Staff-Statistics (Box 76)
    - Statistics (Box 76)
    - Stea-Sz, 4 folders (Box 76)
    - Summer Session-1947 (Box 76)
    - Ta-U, 5 folders (Box 76)
    - University Council (Box 76)
    - University Museums
      - Advisory Board (Box 76)
      - Anthropology (Box 76)
      - Budget (Box 76)
      - E. S. George Reserve (Box 76)
      - Herbarium (Box 76)
      - Lab. Of Vert. Biology (Box 76)
      - Library Committee (Box 76)
      - Operating Committee (Box 76)
      - Paleontology (Box 76)
      - Personnel Data (Box 76)
      - Zoology (Box 76)
    - University Senate (Box 76)
    - Va-Vh (Box 76)
    - Veterans (Box 76)
    - Vi-Wat, 3 folders (Box 76)
    - "War Emergency" or Duration Measures (Box 76)
    - Wau-Wes, 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Wet-Z, 7 folders (Box 77)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 77)
  - 1947-1948
    - Aa-Ak (Box 77)
    - Adams, James P., 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Admissions Estimates Fall 1947 (Box 77)
    - Al-Am (Box 77)
    - American (Box 77)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 77)
    - An-Ar (Box 77)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 77)
    - Appointments (Box 77)
    - As-Az (Box 77)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 77)
    - Baa-Bq, 9 folders (Box 77)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 77)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 77)
    - Bra-Bum, 3 folders (Box 77)
    - Budget 1948-49
      - Department Requests (Box 77)
      - Preliminary Estimates (Box 77)
      - Special Equipment (Box 77)
    - Budget 1947-48
      - Additional Appropriations (Box 77)
      - Deferred Merit Increases (Box 77)
      - Letters (Box 77)
      - Promotions (Box 77)
    - Bun-Chh, 5 folders (Box 77)
    - Center for Japanese Studies (Box 77)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 77)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 77)
    - Chi-Ck (Box 77)
    - Chronological File (Box 77)
    - Church-Related Colleges (Box 77)
    - Cl-Cn (Box 77)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 77)
    - Coa-Cok (Box 77)
    - Codification of Faculty Regulations (Box 77)
    - Col-Con (Box 78)
    - Committees
      - Admission Policies with Respect to Foreign Students (Box 78)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 78)
      - Calendar (Box 78)
      - College Problems (Box 78)
      - Cook Lectureship (Box 78)
      - Cooperation with Educational Institutions (Box 78)
      - Curriculum (Box 78)
      - Dictionaries (Box 78)
      - Library (Box 78)
      - Literary College Building (Box 78)
      - Program in Linguistics (Box 78)
      - Summer Session (Box 78)
    - Conference on Higher Education (February 13-14) (Box 78)
    - Coo-Crn, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Courses (Box 78)
    - Cro-Cz (Box 78)
    - Curriculum-General (Box 78)
    - Daa-Dij, 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Deans' Conference, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Department of State (Box 78)
    - Dik-Eg, 4 folders (Box 78)
    - Eastern Deans' Meeting (Box 78)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 78)
    - Eh-Ez, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - English, Department of (Box 78)
    - English Language Institute, Department of (Box 78)
    - Engineering Research (Box 78)
    - Enrollment
      - Data (Box 78)
      - Estimates-Fall Semester (Box 78)
      - Spring (Box 78)
    - Evaluations, Departmental (Box 78)
    - Evaluation of Faculty Services, Committee on
      - Correspondence (Box 78)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 78)
    - Executive Committee (Box 78)
    - F-Fd (Box 78)
    - Faculty
      - Meetings (Box 78)
      - Minutes (Box 78)
    - Fe-Fk, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Fine Arts, Department of (Box 78)
    - Fl-Gh, 5 folders (Box 78)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 78)
    - Geology, Department of (Box 78)
    - German, Department of (Box 78)
    - Gi-Hok, 13 folders (Box 78)
    - History, Department of (Box 78)
    - Hol-Hos, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Hopwood (Box 78)
    - Hot-Jz, 7 folders (Box 78)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 78)
    - Ka-Kh, 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Keniston's Papers & Requests (Box 78)
    - Ki-Leh, 6 folders (Box 78)
    - Leaves of Absence (Box 78)
    - Lei-Lir, 3 folders (Box 78)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 78)
    - Linguistic Institute (Box 78)
    - Linguistic Society of America (Box 78)
    - Lis-Mb, 6 folders (Box 79)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 79)
    - McA-Mim, 6 folders (Box 79)
    - Michigan College Association (Box 79)
    - Min-Mom (Box 79)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 79)
    - Modern Language Association (Box 79)
    - Mon-Mz, 3 folders (Box 79)
    - Museum of Art (Box 79)
    - Na-Nz, 4 folders (Box 79)
    - Northcentral Association of Colleges (Box 79)
    - Oa-Ol (Box 79)
    - Oriental Languages, Department of (Box 79)
    - Om-Phn, 4 folders (Box 79)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 79)
    - Pho-Pn (Box 79)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 79)
    - Po-Pq (Box 79)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 79)
    - Pr-Pz (Box 79)
    - President's Report (Box 79)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 79)
    - Publications (Box 79)
    - Q-Rek, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Regents' Communications (Box 79)
    - Registrars Office
      - General (Box 79)
      - Statistics (Box 79)
    - Rel-Ric (Box 79)
    - Religion (Box 79)
    - Research Projects (Box 79)
    - Resignations (Box 79)
    - Retirements (Box 79)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 79)
    - Rid-Ros, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 79)
    - Rosen-Rz, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Russian, Department of (Box 79)
    - Saa-Sph, 11 folders (Box 79)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 79)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 79)
    - Spi-Std (Box 79)
    - Statistics (Box 79)
    - Stea-Sz, 4 folders (Box 79)
    - Summer Session (Box 79)
    - Ta-U, 4 folders (Box 79)
    - University Senate (Box 79)
    - University Museums
      - Advisory Board (Box 79)
      - Anthropology (Box 79)
      - Budget (Box 79)
      - E. S. George Reserve (Box 79)
      - Exhibits (Box 79)
      - Herbarium (Box 79)
      - Lab. of Vert. Biology (Box 79)
      - Operating Committee (Box 79)
      - Paleontology (Box 79)
      - Zoology (Box 79)
    - Va-Vh (Box 79)
    - Veterans (Box 79)
    - Vi-Z, 12 folders (Box 79)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 79)
  - 1948-1949
    - Aa-Ak (Box 80)
    - Adams, James P., 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Admissions Estimates
      - Fall (Box 80)
      - Spring (Box 80)
    - Al-Am (Box 80)
    - American (Box 80)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 80)
    - An-Ar (Box 80)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 80)
    - Appointments (Box 80)
    - As-Az (Box 80)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 80)
    - Bam-Bel, 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Beaumarchais Documents (Box 80)
    - Bem-Bq, 4 folders (Box 80)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 80)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 80)
    - Bra-Bum, 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Budget 1948-49
      - Additional Appropriations (Box 80)
    - Budget-Preliminary Estimates 1949-50, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Bun-Bur (Box 80)
    - Bureau of School Services (Box 80)
    - Bus-Chh, 4 folders (Box 80)
    - Center for Japanese Studies (Box 80)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 80)
    - Chemistry, Department of
      - Study (Box 80)
    - Chi-Ck (Box 80)
    - Chronological File (Box 80)
    - Church-Related Colleges (Box 80)
    - Cl-Cn (Box 80)
    - Class of 1919 Award (Box 80)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 80)
    - Col-Con (Box 80)
    - Committees
      - Admission Policies with Respect to Foreign Students (Box 80)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 80)
      - Bureau of School Services (Box 80)
      - Calendar (Box 80)
      - College Problems (Box 80)
      - Cook Lectureship (Box 80)
      - Curriculum (Box 80)
      - Dictionaries (Box 80)
      - Library (Box 80)
      - Program in Linguistics (Box 80)
      - Religion (Box 80)
      - Summer Foreign Study (Box 80)
      - Summer Session (Box 80)
    - Conference on Higher Education, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Coo-Crn, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Courses (Box 80)
    - Cro-Dem, 3 folders (Box 80)
    - Deans' Conference (Box 80)
    - Den-Dij (Box 80)
    - Department of State (Box 80)
    - Dik-Eg, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Eastern Deans' Meeting (Box 80)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 80)
    - Eh-Ez, 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Engineering Research (Box 80)
    - English, Department of (Box 80)
    - English Language Institute (Box 80)
    - Enrollment
      - Estimates-Fall (Box 80)
      - Estimates-Spring (Box 80)
      - Fall (Box 80)
    - Equipment Requests (Box 80)
    - Evaluation of Faculty Services (Box 81)
      - Committee (Box 81)
      - Departmental Committees, 2 folders (Box 81)
      - Student Monitor Lists (Box 81)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 81)
    - Executive Committee (Box 81)
    - F-Fd (Box 81)
    - Faculty Minutes (Box 81)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 81)
    - Fe-Fk, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Fine Arts, Department of (Box 81)
    - Fl-Gh, 5 folders (Box 81)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 81)
    - Geology, Department of (Box 81)
    - German, Department of (Box 81)
    - Goa-Grd, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Grading (Box 81)
    - Graduate School (Box 81)
    - Gre-Hok, 8 folders (Box 81)
    - History, Department of (Box 81)
    - Hol-Hos, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Hopwood (Box 81)
    - Hot-Jz, 7 folders (Box 81)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 81)
    - Ka-Leh, 7 folders (Box 81)
    - Latin American Studies Committee (Box 81)
    - Leave of Absence (Box 81)
    - Lei-Lir, 3 folders (Box 81)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 81)
    - Linguistic Institute (Box 81)
    - Linguistic Society of America (Box 81)
    - Lis-Mb, 6 folders (Box 81)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 81)
    - McD-Mim, 5 folders (Box 81)
    - Michigan College Association (Box 81)
    - Min-Mom (Box 81)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 81)
    - Modern Language Association (Box 81)
    - Mon-New, 5 folders (Box 81)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 81)
    - Newa-Nz, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - North Central Association of Colleges (Box 81)
    - Oa-Oz, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Oriental Languages, Department of (Box 81)
    - Paa-Pen, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Peake, C. H. (Box 81)
    - Peo-Phn (Box 81)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 81)
    - Pho-Pn (Box 81)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 81)
    - Po-Pq (Box 81)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 81)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 81)
    - Pr-Pz (Box 81)
    - President's Report (Box 81)
    - Promotions
      - Departmental Recommendations (Box 81)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 82)
    - Publications (Box 82)
    - Q-Rek, 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Regents' Communications (Box 82)
    - Registrar's Office
      - General (Box 82)
      - Statistics (Box 82)
    - Rel-Ric (Box 82)
    - Religion (Box 82)
    - Research Projects (Box 82)
    - Resignations (Box 82)
    - Retirements (Box 82)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 82)
    - Rid-Roc (Box 82)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 82)
    - Rosen-Rz, 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Russian, Department of
      - Candidates (Box 82)
    - Saa-Sn, 8 folders (Box 82)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 82)
    - Smith-Sph, 2 folders (Box 82)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 82)
    - Spi-Std (Box 82)
    - Statistics (Box 82)
    - Stet-Sz, 3 folders (Box 82)
    - Summer Session (Box 82)
    - Ta-U, 5 folders (Box 82)
    - University Museums (Box 82)
    - University Senate (Box 82)
    - Va-Vh (Box 82)
    - Veterans (Box 82)
    - Vi-Z, 12 folders (Box 82)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 82)
  - 1949-1950
    - A (Box 82)
    - Academic Counselors (Box 82)
    - Adams, James P. (Box 82)
    - Admissions Estimates
      - Spring (Box 82)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 82)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 82)
    - Appointments (Box 82)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 82)
    - B (Box 82)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 82)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 82)
    - Budget 1949-50, 2 folders (Box 83)
      - Additional Appropriations (Box 83)
      - Allocation Sheets (Box 83)
      - Departmental Requests (Box 83)
    - Budget 1950-51
      - Departmental Requests (Box 83)
      - Preliminary Budget (Box 83)
    - Budget Needs 1945-50 (Box 83)
    - Bureau of School Services (Box 83)
    - Caa-Chh, 3 folders (Box 83)
    - Center for Japanese Studies (Box 83)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 83)
    - Chemistry, Department of
      - Study (Box 83)
    - Chi-Ck (Box 83)
    - Chronological File, 6 folders (Box 83)
    - Church-Related Colleges (Box 83)
    - Cl-Cn (Box 83)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 83)
    - Class of 1919 Award (Box 83)
    - Col-Con (Box 83)
    - Committees
      - Advisory (Box 83)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 83)
      - Calendar (Box 83)
      - College Problems (Box 83)
      - Cook Lectureship (Box 83)
      - Curriculum (Box 83)
      - Dictionaries (Box 83)
      - Library (Box 83)
      - Nominating (Box 83)
      - Research (Box 83)
      - Scholarship (Box 83)
      - Summer Session, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Concentration Advisers (Box 83)
    - Conference on Higher Education (Box 83)
    - Coo-Crn, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Courses (Box 83)
    - Cro-Cz (Box 83)
    - Daa-Dem, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Deans' Conference, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Den-Dij (Box 84)
    - Department of State (Box 84)
    - Dos-Eg, 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Eastern Deans' Meeting (Box 84)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 84)
    - Eh-Ez, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Engineering Research (Box 84)
    - English, Department of (Box 84)
    - English Language Institute (Box 84)
    - Enrollment Estimates
      - Fall (Box 84)
      - Spring (Box 84)
    - Equipment (Special) (Box 84)
    - Evaluation of Faculty Services (Box 84)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 84)
    - Executive Committee
      - Minutes (One Set) (Box 84)
    - F-Fd (Box 84)
    - Faculty
      - Committee Reports (Box 84)
      - Meeting Material (Box 84)
      - Minutes (Box 84)
      - Study (Box 84)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 84)
    - Fe-Fh (Box 84)
    - Fellowships (Box 84)
    - Fi-Fk (Box 84)
    - Fine Arts, Department of (Box 84)
    - Fl-Gn, 6 folders (Box 84)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 84)
    - Geology, Department of (Box 84)
    - German, Department of (Box 84)
    - Goa-Grd, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Graduate School (Box 84)
    - Gre-Hd, 6 folders (Box 84)
    - Haven Hall Fire (Box 84)
    - Hea-Hok, 4 folders (Box 84)
    - History, Department of (Box 84)
    - Hol-Hos, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Hopwood (Box 84)
    - Hua-Jz, 5 folders (Box 84)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 84)
    - Ka-Lar, 5 folders (Box 84)
    - Leaves of Absence, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Lei-Lir, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 84)
    - Linguistics, Committee on Program in (Box 84)
    - Linguistic Institute (Box 84)
    - Lis-Mb, 4 folders (Box 84)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 84)
    - McA-Mh, 4 folders (Box 84)
    - Mexican Research 1947-50 (Box 84)
    - Mia-Mim (Box 84)
    - Michigan College Association (Box 84)
    - Min-Mom (Box 84)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 84)
    - Modern Language Association (Box 84)
    - Mors-Nd, 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 84)
    - Newa-Nz, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - North Central Association of Colleges (Box 84)
    - Oa-Pen, 4 folders (Box 85)
    - Peake, C. H. (Box 85)
    - Peo-Phn (Box 85)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 85)
    - Pho-Pn (Box 85)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 85)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 85)
    - Po-Pq (Box 85)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 85)
    - Pr-Pz (Box 85)
    - President's Report (Box 85)
    - Promotions
      - Salary Increases (Form C's) (Box 85)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 85)
    - Publications (Box 85)
    - Q-Rek, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Regents' Communications (Box 85)
    - Registrar's Office
      - Director of Admissions (Box 85)
      - General (Box 85)
      - Statistics (Box 85)
    - Rel-Ric (Box 85)
    - Religion (Box 85)
    - Research
      - Instructional (Box 85)
      - Projects (Box 85)
    - Resignations (Box 85)
    - Retirements (Box 85)
    - Reunion Breakfast (Box 85)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 85)
    - Rid-Ros, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 85)
    - Rosen-Rz, 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Russian, Department of (Box 85)
    - Saa-Sph, 10 folders (Box 85)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 85)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 85)
    - Spi-Std (Box 85)
    - Statistics (Box 85)
    - Stet-Sz, 3 folders (Box 85)
    - Summer Session (Box 85)
    - Ta-U, 4 folders (Box 85)
    - University Museums (Box 85)
    - University Senate (Box 85)
    - Va-Z, 13 folders (Box 85)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 85)
  - 1950-1951
    - Aa-Ak (Box 86)
    - Academic Counselors (Box 86)
    - Adams, James P. (Box 86)
    - Admissions
      - Estimates for Fall (Box 86)
      - Spring (Box 86)
      - Summer (Box 86)
    - Al-Am (Box 86)
    - American (Box 86)
    - An-Ar (Box 86)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 86)
    - Appointments (Box 86)
    - Area Programs (Box 86)
    - Armed Services (Box 86)
    - As-Az (Box 86)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 86)
    - Baa-Bk, 6 folders (Box 86)
    - Biological Station & Biological Sciences 1946-51 (Box 86)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 86)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 86)
    - Bra-Brt, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Budget 1950-51, 2 folders
      - Additional Appropriations and Transfers (Box 86)
      - Allocation Sheets (Box 86)
      - Special Equipment (Box 86)
    - Budget 1951-52
      - Departmental Requests (Box 86)
    - Building Needs (Box 86)
    - Bun-Bur (Box 86)
    - Bureau of School Services (Box 86)
    - Bus-Chh, 5 folders (Box 86)
    - Center for Japanese Studies (Box 86)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 86)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 86)
    - Chi-Ck (Box 86)
    - Church-Related Colleges (Box 86)
    - Cl-Cn (Box 86)
    - Class of 1919 Award (Box 86)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 86)
    - Col-Con (Box 86)
    - Committees
      - Admissions Advisory (Box 86)
      - Barbour Scholarship (Box 86)
      - Calendar (Box 86)
      - College Problems (Box 86)
      - College Relations (Box 86)
      - Cook Lectureship (Box 86)
      - Curriculum (Box 86)
      - Deanship 1949-51 (Box 86)
      - Dictionaries (Box 86)
      - Fact Finding (Box 86)
      - Library (Box 86)
      - Nominating (Box 86)
      - Scholarship (Box 86)
      - Summer Session (Box 86)
    - Concentration Advisers (Box 86)
    - Conference on Higher Education, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Coo-Crn, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Courses (Box 86)
    - Cro-Cz (Box 86)
    - Daa-Dem, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Deans (Box 87)
    - Deans' Conference, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Den-Dij (Box 87)
    - Department of State (Box 87)
    - Dik-Dz, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Dutch Professorship 1949-51 (Box 87)
    - Ea-Eg (Box 87)
    - Eastern Deans' Meeting (Box 87)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 87)
    - Eh-Ez, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Engineering Research (Box 87)
    - English, Department of (Box 87)
    - English Language Institute (Box 87)
    - English-Speaking Union (Box 87)
    - Enrollment
      - Data (misc.) (Box 87)
      - Estimates for Fall (Box 87)
    - Equipment (Special) (Box 87)
    - Evaluation of Faculty Services, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 87)
    - Executive Committee
      - Meeting December 6, 1950 (Box 87)
    - Fa-Fd (Box 87)
    - Faculty Meeting
      - Material (Box 87)
      - Minutes (Box 87)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 87)
    - Fe-Fh (Box 87)
    - Fellowships (Box 87)
    - Fi-Fk (Box 87)
    - Fine Arts, Department of (Box 87)
    - Fl-Gh, 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 87)
    - Geology, Department of (Box 87)
    - German, Department of (Box 87)
    - Gi-Grd, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Graduate School (Box 87)
    - Gri-Hok, 7 folders (Box 87)
    - History, Department of (Box 87)
    - Hol-Hoo (Box 87)
    - Hopwood (Box 87)
    - Hua-I, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - International Center (Box 87)
    - Ja-Jz, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 87)
    - Ka-Kh, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Keniston's Papers & Requests 1948-51 (Box 87)
    - Ki-Leh, 5 folders (Box 87)
    - Latin American Program 1947-51 (Box 87)
    - Leaves of Absence (Box 87)
    - Lei-Lir, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 87)
    - Linguistics, Committee on Program in (Box 87)
    - Linguistic Institute (Box 87)
    - Lis-Mb, 2 folders (Box 87)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 87)
    - McD-Mim, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Michigan College Association (Box 87)
    - Min-Mom (Box 87)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 87)
    - Modern Language Association (Box 87)
    - Mon-Mz, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Na-Nd (Box 88)
    - Natural Science Shop (Box 88)
    - Nea-New (Box 88)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 88)
    - Needs of the College, 1945-52 (Box 88)
    - Newa-Nz, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Northern Central Association of Colleges (Box 88)
    - Oa-Phn, 5 folders (Box 88)
    - Perkins, John A. (Box 88)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 88)
    - Pho-Pn (Box 88)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 88)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 88)
    - Pierpont, W. K. (Box 88)
    - Po-Pq (Box 88)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 88)
    - Pr-Pz (Box 88)
    - President's Report (Box 88)
    - Promotions, 2 folders
      - Salary Increases (Form C's) (Box 88)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 88)
    - Publications (Box 88)
    - Q-Rat (Box 88)
    - Regents' Communications (Box 88)
    - Registrar's Office
      - Director of Admissions (Box 88)
      - General (Box 88)
      - Statistics (Box 88)
    - Rel-Ric (Box 88)
    - Religion (Box 88)
    - Research Projects (Box 88)
    - Resignations (Box 88)
    - Retirements
      - By Years Until 1950 (Box 88)
    - Rid-Roc (Box 88)
    - Robertson, James H. (Box 88)
    - Rod-Ros (Box 88)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 88)
    - Rosen-Rz, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Russian, Department of (Box 88)
    - Saa-Sph, 8 folders (Box 88)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 88)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 88)
    - Spi-Std (Box 88)
    - Statistics (Box 88)
    - Stea-Sz, 4 folders (Box 88)
    - Summer Session (Box 88)
    - Ta-Tg (Box 88)
    - Television (Box 88)
    - Th-Tn (Box 88)
    - Thanksgiving Absences (Box 88)
    - To-Trh (Box 88)
    - Travel (Box 88)
    - U (Box 89)
    - University Museums (Box 89)
    - University Senate (Box 89)
    - Va-Y, 11 folders (Box 89)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 89)
  - 1951-1952
    - Aa-Ak (Box 89)
    - Academic Counselors (Box 89)
    - Acceptances (Box 89)
    - Admissions for Fall (Box 89)
    - Al-Am (Box 89)
    - American (Box 89)
    - An-Ar (Box 89)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 89)
    - Appointments (Box 89)
    - Armed Services (Box 89)
    - As-Az (Box 89)
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 89)
    - Baa-Bi, 4 folders (Box 89)
    - Biophysics 1949-52 (Box 89)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 89)